We got a nice looking application we added a lot of functionality over the last lectures,
Gzel bir uygulama bulduk, son derslerde bir sr fonksiyonellik ekledik.
now of course we want to have a really good application not only by the looks of it but also by the
phesiz elbette, sadece grnyle deil, ayn zamanda yapm biimimizle de iyi bir uygulamaya sahip
way we structure it,
olmak istiyoruz.
we work with it. Now throughout building this application,
Artk bu uygulamay oluturmakla birlikte alyoruz.
I already showed you a lot of best practices for building that, I shared my thought process on how to
Zanaatkrmda, uygulamann nasl yaplacan ve planlandracam konusunda dnce srecimi paylatmz belletmeniz iin bir sr en
structure and plan the application and I gave you some alternatives at some points of time on how you may
iyi uygulamalar gsterdim ve bir takm eleri paralara ayrma eklinizle ilgili baz
split something into components.
zaman noktalarnda baz alternatifler vereceim.
Here we actually have a relatively granular component structure,
Burada aslnda greceli olarak ayrntl bir bileen yapmz var.
you could certainly combine some of the components we're using
Kesinlikle, kullandmz baz bileenleri birletirebilirsin.
but can you also improve some things.
Ancak baz eyleri de gelitirebilir misin?
Let's dive into two important things we learned about, prop types and pure components.
imdi, Propp trleri ve saf bileenler hakknda rendiimiz iki nemli bilgiye dalalm.
So in shouldComponentUpdate
Yani ksa bir bileen gncelleme.
and let's also have a look at all these lifecycle methods you learned about in general.
Ayrca, genel olarak rendiiniz tm yaam dngs yntemlerine bir gz atalm.
Do we use them in there?
Onlar orada kullanyor muyuz
Why don't we use them at any point right now? Where would we use them?
Neden onlar nerede kullanacamz bir noktada kullanmyoruz?
Let's answer these questions over the next lectures.
Bu sorular bir sonraki ders boyunca cevaplayalm.